Raji Ayub O.

https://ayyubraji.netlify.app | https://github.com/Qodemi | rajiayubaozovehe@gmail.com

+234 (0) 814 501 4012

Summary

Hi, I'm Raji Ayub Ozovehe, a web developer specializing in front end development. I build responsive websites with creative designs and experience, which are also scalable and user-friendly with neat, readable and maintainable code.

Skill-set and Tools

HTML5 | JavaScript | React | Tailwind | Bootstrap | CSS | PHP | SQL | Git and GitHub | Netlify | VSCode | Arduino IDE(Embedded C) | Wokwi

Experience

FEBRUARY 2023 - PRESENT

Rajtronix-Technologies, Ibadan - Web Developer

- Collaborating with developers and hardware engineers on IOT based projects, developing
 interactive and responsive user interface, web apps to handle forms and online data for IoT and
 smart devices.
- Developed a website for a company, Poiselar, Lagos. The structure has pages for the company's major business on Home automation and gadgets, Photography/Videography and Luxury/Furnitures.
- Worked as front-end developer in building a fully functioning e-commerce website, tmms.ng

Technologies: Arduino IDE | VS Code | React | PHP |

DECEMBER 2024 (Remote Contract)

Vast Creations, Lagos. - Front-end Developer

• Built a React.Js landing page with dynamic and responsive interface for the STEM Organisation, Vast Creations, Lagos. - *vastcreation.tech*

July 2023 - August 2023 (Young Inventors Summer Camp)

Center4Tech, Lagos – LEAD INSTRUCTOR

Deployed on a contract as Lead Instructor together with a team of Eight from the company to one
of its nine Centers, Kids Court School, Surulere, Lagos. For a 5 week STEM program featuring
Electronics/Robotics, Web design, Mobile App, Mobile Games, and Tech discovery.

Technologies: Arduino and Arduino IDE | VS Code | Construct3 | MIT App Inventor || HTML5, CSS, JavaScript | Arduino Programming

Education

National Certificate of Education: Mathematics/Physics - 2019-2023

Osun State College of Education, Nigeria.

Projects

- Responsive web pages: <u>Vastcreations.tech</u> (STEM Landing page), <u>tmms.ng</u> (E-commerce website),
 rajtronixtech.com, <u>ceostatusviews.com</u>.
- Weather App: A responsive and functioning API application that fetches weather data online and displays the data categorically temperature, humidity, weather condition etc. in a well arranged and user friendly interface.
- Replication of some commendable websites' interface and responsiveness: Jumia replicate, w3schools replicate, youtube replicate.